As interdependent beings we cannot thrive independent of others.
作为相互依存的生命，我们离开他人便无法茁壮成长。
We like to work with people who are like-minded, with whom we share a common interest, or who also believe in a cause we are serious about.
我们喜欢和这样的人共事：志同道合、与我们有共同利益，或者同样认同我们真心投入的某项事业。
This is evident in how we have organized ourselves into various collective groups such as nations, regions, communities, organizations, and families.
从我们把自己组织成国家、地区、社区、组织、家庭等各种集体的方式中，这一点显而易见。
Does the group you belong to have a strong collective consciousness or shared beliefs?
你所属的群体有强烈的集体意识或共同信念吗？
Is there interdependence among its members?
群体成员之间相互依存吗？
Do you consider this group a significant part of your existence?
你认为这个群体是你人生的重要组成部分吗？
If your answers are affirmative, then you are experiencing a micro version of solidarity.
如果你的回答是肯定的，那么你正在体验一种微缩版的团结。
What is solidarity?
什么是团结？
Its simplest definition in the dictionary is: “… a unifying opinion, feeling, purpose or interest among a group of people.”
词典对它最简单的定义是：“……一群人之间起凝聚作用的观点、情感、目的或利益。”
In this increasingly diverse society we live in, solidarity takes on a complex and multifaceted character as it forms bonds of interdependence among unique individuals living in a fast-changing environment and working within a complex division of labor.
在我们所生活的这个日益多元的社会中，团结呈现出复杂而多面的特点，因为它在一个个独特的个体之间形成相互依存的纽带，而这些个体生活在快速变化的环境中，在复杂的劳动分工体系下工作。
One facet of solidarity fits well with the principles of communitarianism.
团结的一个侧面与社群主义的原则十分契合。
In this setting, individuals give up their own interests to serve the common good.
在这种情形下，个人为了服务于公共利益而放弃自身利益。
However, its strict adherence to social cohesiveness and exclusiveness restricts expression and practice of individual differences and preferences.
然而，这种团结严格坚守社会凝聚性和排他性，从而限制了个人差异与偏好的表达和践行。
Consequently, individuality and autonomy are sacrificed to maintain the unity of the group.
因此，为了维护群体的统一，个性和自主性遭到了牺牲。
Solidarity is also viewed as a reaction to the extreme emphasis on individualism and freedom of choice.
团结也被视为对极端强调个人主义和选择自由的一种反应。
It goes against the liberal idea of unrestricted individuals who see society as a hindrance to their freedom to make choices and to act according to what is good for them regardless of how these will affect others.
它违背了自由主义的一种观念，即个人不受约束，把社会视为一种阻碍，妨碍他们自由地做出选择、按照对自己有利的方式行事，而不顾这些选择和行为会对他人产生什么影响。
But despite its many facets, social theorists have viewed solidarity as a key factor in bringing about order and progress in society.
不过，尽管团结有诸多侧面，社会理论家一直把它视为带来社会秩序与进步的关键因素。
They believe that for human society to survive as it becomes more diverse, more new bonds need to be formed based on the differences.
他们认为，人类社会要在变得更加多元的同时存续下去，就需要以这些差异为基础，形成更多新的纽带。
In the light of this, they regard a genuine solidarity as more than just shallow relationships based on common interests.
鉴于此，他们认为真正的团结不仅仅是基于共同利益的浅层关系。
Solidarity is not just a product of strategic calculations of how much it will benefit the self.
团结并不只是策略性地盘算它能给自己带来多少好处的产物。
It is not an exclusive class founded on the you-and-me-against-the-world principle.
它不是建立在“你我联手对抗全世界”这一原则之上的排他性群体。
Rather, it is inclusive and is not forced.
相反，它是包容的，而且不是强制的。
Acting out of solidarity means supporting and standing up for each other—in recognition that one’s fate is in the fate of the other.
出于团结而行动，意味着彼此支持、相互维护，因为认识到一个人的命运就寓于他人的命运之中。
It is a bond characterized by cooperative practices and strengthened by the concern for the well-being of others or the common good.
它是一种以合作实践为特征的纽带，又因关心他人的福祉或公共利益而更加牢固。
It fights for the protection of human dignity and listens to and acts on the cries of the most vulnerable.
它为保护人的尊严而斗争，倾听最弱势群体的呼声，并据此采取行动。